Maria Fernanda Auzaque Fernandez

BILINGUAL RECRUITER

+57 3165770353

fernanda.auzaque@solvogoblal.com

Bucaramanga, Colombia

Bilingual lawyer with professional experience in the public and private sectors, focused on civil and constitutional law issues. With leadership and organization skills, a high sense of commitment and fast learning abilities, Skills developed in Microsoft Suite like Excel, PowerPoint and Word. Currently working as a Solvo recruiter, involved in talent acquisition processes specialized in recruitment.

EDUCATION

Lawyer Degree 2013-2019 High School Graduate 2012

Universidad Autónoma de Bucaramanga

Instituto Caldas

EXPERIENCE

Bilingual Recruiter
July 2022 - Currently

Solvo Global
Multitasking and time management
skills and abilities to manage social
media and job platforms.

Court Reporter "Escribiente" Jan 2021 - May 2022

J27 Municipal Civil Court Bucaramanga. Lawyer responsible of constitutional actions, sending official communications and all of those functions entrusted by the judge. Junior Lawyer Oct 2019 - Dec 2020

C.R. Legal Services S.A.S.
Junior lawyer in charge of
substantiation, presentation and
monitoring of executive processes,
management of constitutional actions
and projection of legal documents.

SKILLS

Languages

- English level B2
- Native Spanish

Soft skills

- Leadership
- Active listening
- Fast learning
- Teamwork
- · Work ethic

Hard Skills

- Microsoft Suite
- Human resources processes
- Recruitment platforms